Guide to the Yale University Library Name/Title Card Catalog
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Faria (Box 2422)
- Farjeon (Box 2423)
- Farmer, J. (Box 2424)
- Farnell (Box 2425)
- Farquhar, H. (Box 2426)
- Farrell (Box 2427)
- Farson, Daniel (Box 2428)
- Fasnacht (Box 2429)
- Fatal Secret (Box 2430)
- Fatt, Irving (Box 2431)
- Faulkner, Herbert (Box 2432)
- Faulmann (Box 2433)
- Faurey (Box 2434)
- Faust (Puppet-Play) (Box 2435)
- Favill (Box 2436)
- Fawn (Box 2437)
- Faysal 'Awn (Box 2438)
- Featley (Box 2439)
- Feder (Box 2440)
- Federal Fisheries (Box 2441)
- Federal Reserve Bank (Box 2442)
- Federalist (Box 2443)
- Federation of Free Farmers (Box 2444)
- Fedorets, I.V. (Box 2445)
- Feer (Box 2446)
- Fei hui tsu (Box 2447)
- Feil (Box 2448)
- Feis, H. (Box 2449)
- Feldman, B. (Box 2450)
- Feline, A. (Box 2451)
- Feller, W. (Box 2452)
- Felsina pittrice (Box 2453)
- Feminist aesthetics (Box 2454)
- Fenelon (Box 2455)
- Feng fan (Box 2456)
- Feng-shui (Box 2457)
- Fenimore (Box 2458)
- Fenollosa, M. (Box 2459)
- Fera, D. (Box 2460)
- Feres, N.T. (Box 2461)
- Ferguson, Robert (Box 2462)
- Ferman, B. (Box 2463)
- Fernandez, Doreen (Box 2464)
- Fernandez de Aviles, A. (Box 2465)
- Fernandez Mac-Gregor, G. (Box 2466)
- Fernhout, J. (Box 2467)
- Ferrari, B. (Box 2468)
- Ferreira, D. (Box 2469)
- Ferrero (Box 2470)
- Ferris (Box 2471)
- Fertility (Box 2472)
- Festgabe (Box 2473)
- Festschrift… Litzman (Box 2474)
- Fete batrine (Box 2475)
- Feuerbach (Box 2476)
- Fever (Box 2477)
- Fi al-sama (Box 2478)
- Fichte, Johann G. (Box 2479)
- Ficker, W. (Box 2480)
- Fiedler, K. (Box 2481)
- Field, J. (Box 2482)
- Field Museum of Natural History (Box 2483)
- Fielding, Henry. History of Tom Jones, 1834 (Box 2484)
- Fields, Dorothy (continued) (Box 2485)
- Fierro, P. (Box 2486)
- Fifty m. (Box 2487)
- Fighting r. (Box 2488)
- Figuraciones (Box 2489)
- Filar, A. (Box 2490)
- Filipinas y Mexico (Box 2491)
- Filliou, R. (Box 2492)
- Films of W. (Box 2493)
- Filosofskie t. (Box 2494)
- Final report W. (Box 2495)
- Financial r. (Box 2496)
- Finanzierungen (Box 2497)
- Finding facts (Box 2498)
- Fine Gael (Box 2499)
- Fink, G. (Box 2500)
- Finland N. (Box 2501)
- Finn (Box 2502)
- Finska (Box 2503)
- Firbank (Box 2504)
- Firestone Plantations Company (Box 2505)
- First considerations (Box 2506)
- First part (Box 2507)
- Fiscal (Box 2508)
- Fischer, Ernst (Box 2509)
- Fischer, K. (Box 2510)
- Fischer, Wolfram (Box 2511)
- Fishbein, M. (Box 2512)
- Fisher, H. (Box 2513)
- Fisher, K.A. (Box 2514)
- Fisher, William L. (Box 2515)
- Fisk, O. (Box 2516)
- Fitch, G. (Box 2517)
- Fitzcarrald, C.F. (Box 2518)
- Fitzgerald, Sally (Box 2519)
- Fitzpatrick, V. (Box 2520)
- Five power (Box 2521)
- Flack (Box 2522)
- Flament (Box 2523)
- Flasch (Box 2524)
- Flaubert and Turgenev (Box 2525)
- Fleeson, E. (Box 2526)
- Fleisig (Box 2527)
- Fleming, W. (Box 2528)
- Fletcher, G. (Box 2529)
- Fletcher, Julia (Box 2530)
- Fleury, Jules (Box 2531)
- Flies (surname) (Box 2532)
- Flint family (Box 2533)
- Floquelmont (Box 2534)
- Florence. Camera (Box 2535)
- Flores, J. (Box 2536)
- Florian, M. (Box 2537)
- Florida Historical Society (Box 2538)
- Flory (Box 2539)
- Flowers (surname) (Box 2540)
- Flugschriften (Box 2541)
- Flynn, H. (Box 2542)
- Fock (Box 2543)
- Foelster (Box 2544)
- Foerstl (Box 2545)
- Fogo (Box 2546)
- Foley (Box 2547)
- Folk art (Box 2548)
- Folklore feminists' (Box 2549)
- Following (Box 2550)
- Fondation (Box 2551)
- Fondo de D. (Box 2552)
- Fonseca, R. (Box 2553)
- Fontana h. (Box 2554)
- Fontes B. (Box 2555)
- Food and Agriculture Organization of the U.N. (Box 2556)
- Food and Agriculture Organization of the U.N. (Agriculture Division) (Box 2557)
- Foodstuffs (Box 2558)
- Foote, Samuel (subject) (Box 2559)
- For y. (Box 2560)
- Forbes, Robert H. (Box 2561)
- Ford (surname) (Box 2562)
- Ford, J. (Box 2563)
- Ford, W. (Box 2564)
- Fordingbridge (Box 2565)
- Foreign language (Box 2566)
- Foreign trade (Box 2567)
- Forest (titles, etc.) (Box 2568)
- Forestville (Box 2569)
- Form (titles, phrases, etc.) (Box 2570)
- Forman, Lewis (Box 2571)
- Formirovanie (Box 2572)
- Foro E. (Box 2573)
- Forschungen und… (Box 2574)
- Forschungsberichte Islamische (Box 2575)
- Forster, Edward Morgan (subject) (Box 2576)
- Forsyth, P. (Box 2577)
- Forte (Box 2578)
- Fortoul (Box 2579)
- Forty (Box 2580)
- Foscolo (Box 2581)
- Fossin (Box 2582)
- Foster, John (Box 2583)
- Foster, W. (Box 2584)
- Foucart (Box 2585)
- Foular (Box 2586)
- Foundations of… (Box 2587)
- Fouquet, Pierre (Box 2588)
- Four years of… (Box 2589)
- Fournier, P. (Box 2590)
- Fowler, D.H. (Box 2591)
- Fowler, William Chauncey (Box 2592)
- Fox, F. (Box 2593)
- Fox, R. (Box 2594)
- Foxley, Alejandro (Box 2595)
- Fraenkel (Box 2596)
- Fragmentaria (Box 2597)
- Framing (Box 2598)
- France, Anna Kay (Box 2599)
- France (Laws, statutes, etc.) (N) (Box 2600)
- France. Armee. Cavalerie-Drill (Box 2601)
- France. Asifat (Box 2602)
- France. Bibliotheque Nationale. Inventaire general (Box 2603)
- France. Chambre des deputes (Box 2604)
- France. Conseil d'Etat (continued) (Box 2605)
- France. Depot de la guerre (Box 2606)
- France. Imprimerie Nationale (Box 2607)
- France. Ministere de l'Interieur (Box 2608)
- France. Ministere des Affaires Etrangeres. Documents diplomatiques (Box 2609)
- France. Parlement (Paris) (Box 2610)
- France. Sovereigns (Box 2611)
- France Afrique (Box 2612)
- Franceschi, R. (Box 2613)
- Francesco d'Assisi (Box 2614)
- Francis, P. (Box 2615)
- Franciscans (titles, phrases, etc.) (Box 2616)
- Franck, J. (Box 2617)
- Franco, Leon (Box 2618)
- Francotte (Box 2619)
- Frank, I. (Box 2620)
- Frank der Funfte (Box 2621)
- Franken (Box 2622)
- Frankfurt Chronik (Box 2623)
- Franklin (Box 2624)
- Franklin, Benjamin (Autobiography and…) (Box 2625)
- Franklin, Benjamin, 1706-1790. Poor Richard (subject) (Box 2626)
- Franklin, Benjamin, 1706-1790-Bibliography (Box 2627)
- Franklin, Benjamin, 1706-1790-Religion (Box 2628)
- Franklin Institute (Box 2629)
- Fransman, L. (Box 2630)
- Franz L. (Box 2631)
- Fraser, C. (Box 2632)
- Fraser, William H. (Box 2633)
- Frauenlob, D. (Box 2634)
- Frech (Box 2635)
- Frederick II, der Grosse, King of Prussia.(F) (Box 2636)
- Frederix, P. (Box 2637)
- Free-man (Box 2638)
- Freedman, M. David (Box 2639)
- Freeholders society (Box 2640)
- Freeman, L. (Box 2641)
- Freemasons. Costa-Rica (Box 2642)
- Freemasons-History-Sources (Box 2643)
- Freiberg, W. (Box 2644)
- Freie Universitat Berlin (Box 2645)
- Freire, P. (Box 2646)
- Fremon, C.F. (Box 2647)
- French, R.A. (Box 2648)
- French literature (Box 2649)
- Frenkel (Box 2650)
- Freri (Box 2651)
- Freud, S. (author) (Box 2652)
- Freud, Sigmund (subject) (S) (Box 2653)
- Freunde (Box 2654)
- Freyer (Box 2655)
- Fribourg (Box 2656)
- Fridrichsen (Box 2657)
- Friedensburg, W. (Box 2658)
- Friedlander (Box 2659)
- Friedman, M. (Box 2660)
- Friedrich Wilhelm I, Duke of Saxony (Box 2661)
- Friedrich Hebbel (Box 2662)
- Friend to America (Box 2663)
- Friendship (titles, phrases, etc.) (Box 2664)
- Friis, H. (Box 2665)
- Frisch, R. (Box 2666)
- Fritschler, A. Lee (Box 2667)
- Froebel (Box 2668)
- Froidmont (Box 2669)
- From exile… (Box 2670)
- From sect… (Box 2671)
- Fromentin, E. (Box 2672)
- Fronte (Box 2673)
- Frossard, A. (Box 2674)
- Frot, J. (Box 2675)
- Fruehling (Box 2676)
- Fry, E. (Box 2677)
- Fryer, H. (Box 2678)
- Fu, Heng (Box 2679)
- Fu shih (Box 2680)
- Fuchs, Arno (Box 2681)
- Fuder, D. (Box 2682)
- Fuenn, S. (Box 2683)
- Fuerst (Box 2684)
- Fugger family (Box 2685)
- Fujii, Y. (Box 2686)
- Fujita, Tokutaro (Box 2687)
- Fukai, I. (Box 2688)
- Fukujin (Box 2689)
- Fulbright grants (Box 2690)
- Fuller, Anna (Box 2691)
- Fuller, S. (Box 2692)
- Fulton, John Farquhar (N) (Box 2693)
- Funcke (Box 2694)
- Fundacio (Box 2695)
- Fundamentals (Box 2696)
- Funk, D. (Box 2697)
- Furche (Box 2698)
- Furness, J.R. (Box 2699)
- Further data (Box 2700)
- Fusees (Box 2701)
- Futbol (Box 2702)
- Future positive (Box 2703)
- G., B. (Box 2704)
- G.R.G. (Box 2705)
- Gabin (Box 2706)
- Gabriel, R. (Box 2707)
- Gad (Box 2708)
- Gadzhi-zade (Box 2709)
- Gaffe (Box 2710)
- Gagne (Box 2711)
- Gaile (Box 2712)
- Gaiser (Box 2713)
- Gakumon (Box 2714)
- Galassi (Box 2715)
- Gale, L. (Box 2716)
- Galerie (Box 2717)
- Galerie Marcel Guiot (Box 2718)
- Galiano (Box 2719)
- Galineta (Box 2720)
- Gallandi, A. (Box 2721)
- Gallegos, S. (Box 2722)
- Gallert (Box 2723)
- Gallipolis, O. (Box 2724)
- Galluppi (Box 2725)
- Galsworthy, John (subject) (Box 2726)
- Galvez (Box 2727)
- Gambetta (Box 2728)
- Game t. (Box 2729)
- Gamst (Box 2730)
- Gandhi (subject) (Box 2731)
- Gandy, R.O. (Box 2732)
- Gankin (Box 2733)
- Gant (Box 2734)
- Garagorri (Box 2735)
- Garbit (Box 2736)
- Garcia, L. (Box 2737)
- Garcia Cipres (Box 2738)
- Garcia Lorca (Box 2739)
- Garcia Pabon (Box 2740)
- Garcke (Box 2741)
- Gardet (Box 2742)
- Gardiner, ME (Box 2743)
- Gardner, John C. (Box 2744)
- Garfield (Box 2745)
- Garin (Box 2746)
- Garland Reference Library of Social Science (continued) (v. 217) (Box 2747)
- Garner, R. (Box 2748)
- Garnier, R. (Box 2749)
- Garrett, Joao Baptista (Box 2750)
- Garrido Espinoza, A. (Box 2751)
- Garshin (Box 2752)
- Garvey (Box 2753)
- Gasch (Box 2754)
- Gaspar, Margit (Box 2755)
- Gass (Box 2756)
- Gataker (Box 2757)
- Gathorne-Hardy (Box 2758)
- Gaubius (Box 2759)
- Gauger (Box 2760)
- Gaultier (Box 2761)
- Gauthier, J. (Box 2762)
- Gautrelet (Box 2763)
- Gawain (Box 2764)
- Gay, John (The Wife of Bath) (Box 2765)
- Gaylord (Box 2766)
- Gazetteer P. (Box 2767)
- Gebauerova (Box 2768)
- Geddes (Box 2769)
- Gee, W. (Box 2770)
- Gegenbaur, Karl (Box 2771)
- Geib (Box 2772)
- Geikie, J. (Box 2773)
- Geissler (Box 2774)
- Gekht, S. (Box 2775)
- Gelee (Box 2776)
- Gelli (Box 2777)
- Gemeindebrett (Box 2778)
- Gendai (Box 2779)
- Gendai Nihon gaka ron (Box 2780)
- Gendai taishu bungaku... (Box 2781)
- Genealogy (titles, etc.) (Box 2782)
- General congregational (Box 2783)
- General magazine (Box 2784)
- General Tire and Rubber Company (Box 2785)
- Genesis and geology (Box 2786)
- Genetics, evolution, and man (Box 2787)
- Genevoix (Box 2788)
- Genji (Box 2789)
- Genoa, Museo (Box 2790)
- Gensler (Box 2791)
- Gentillet (Box 2792)
- Gentry (Box 2793)
- Geoffrin (Box 2794)
- Geografisk (Box 2795)
- Geographische Gesellschaft (Box 2796)
- Geological Society of America (Box 2797)
- Geological Survey (U.S.) Division of Hydrography (Box 2798)
- Geologische (Box 2799)
- Georg (Box 2800)
- George, Saint (Box 2801)
- George, T. (Box 2802)
- George Peabody College for Teachers. Division of Surveys (Box 2803)
- Georgetown, Mass. (Box 2804)
- Georgia. Department of Mines (Box 2805)
- Georgian poetry (Box 2806)
- Gera, 1720-1797 (Box 2807)
- Gerasimov (Box 2808)
- Gere (Box 2809)
- Gerhartz (Box 2810)
- Germain (Box 2811)
- German-Jewish periodicals (Box 2812)
- Germane (Box 2813)
- Germann (Box 2814)
- Germany. Heer (author) (Box 2815)
- Germany. Laws, statutes, etc. (Box 2816)
- Germany. Reichsbank (Box 2817)
- Germany. Treaties, etc., 1925- (Box 2818)
- Germany (Democratic Republic, 1949-) (Box 2819)
- Germany (West) (Box 2820)
- Germany (West). Nationalgalerie (continued) (Box 2821)
- Germany (Federal Republic, 1949- ). Statistisches Bundesamt. Index (Box 2822)
- Germany (titles, etc.) (Box 2823)
- Gerome (Box 2824)
- Gershwin, George (author) (Box 2825)
- Gerstaecker (Box 2826)
- Gervais (Box 2827)
- Geschichte (Box 2828)
- Geschichte des (Box 2829)
- Geschichtswissenschaft (Box 2830)
- Gesellschaft fuer erdkunde (Box 2831)
- Gesellschaft naturforschender (Box 2832)
- Gesner, Konrad (author) (Box 2833)
- Geste (Box 2834)
- Getto (Box 2835)
- Geyer (Box 2836)
- Ghana (Box 2837)
- Ghasali (Box 2838)
- Gheon (Box 2839)
- Ghiron (Box 2840)
- Ghosh (Box 2841)
- Giacconi, Riccardo (Box 2842)
- Giannini (Box 2843)
- Gibbes (Box 2844)
- Gibbs, G (Box 2845)
- Gibran (Box 2846)
- Gibson, K. (Box 2847)
- Gide (Box 2848)
- Giedion (Box 2849)
- Giesen, W. (Box 2850)
- Gifford, W. (Box 2851)
- Gihl (Box 2852)
- Gilberg (Box 2853)
- Gilbert, M. (Box 2854)
- Gilbertson (Box 2855)
- Giles (Box 2856)
- Gilkerson, W. (Box 2857)
- Gilland, W. (Box 2858)
- Gillett, J.D. (Box 2859)
- Gillman, P. (Box 2860)
- Gilmore (Box 2861)
- Gilson, Etienne H. (subject) (Box 2862)
- Ginger (Box 2863)
- Ginsi (Box 2864)
- Giono (Box 2865)
- Giorni (Box 2866)
- Gippius, A. (Box 2867)
- Girard (Box 2868)
- Girdler (Box 2869)
- Gironde (France) (Box 2870)
- Gissing (Box 2871)
- Giuliani (Box 2872)
- Given (Box 2873)
- Gladkov (Box 2874)
- Glaisher (Box 2875)
- Glaser, E. (Box 2876)
- Glass (Box 2877)
- Glastonbury (Box 2878)
- Glazier (Box 2879)
- Gleiss (Box 2880)
- Glicenstein, Henryk (Box 2881)
- Gloag (Box 2882)
- Gloeckner (Box 2883)
- Glossary of Railwaymen's Talk (Box 2884)
- Glowacki, Ryszard (Box 2885)
- Glushko, M. (Box 2886)
- Gnevko, Valentina (Box 2887)
- Gobert, Adrienne (Box 2888)
- God Save The Mark (Box 2889)
- Gode (Box 2890)
- Godin (Box 2891)
- Godoy Gallardo, Eduardo (Box 2892)
- Goebbels, Josef (Box 2893)
- Goeke (Box 2894)
- Goerland (Box 2895)
- Goeteborg (Sweden) Stadsbiblioteket (Box 2896)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von. Conversations (Box 2897)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von. Individual Works. Erwin and Elmire (Box 2898)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von. Individual Works. Faust. Selections (Box 2899)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von. Individual Works. Faust. Study. (Box 2900)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von. Individual Works. Novelle. (Box 2901)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von. Individual works. Versuch die metamorphose… (Box 2902)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von (subject) (Box 2903)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von-Biography (E) (Box 2904)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von-Friends and Associates (Box 2905)
- Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von-Music (Box 2906)
- Goethe, Walther Wolfgang Von. Allegro (Box 2907)
- Goette (Box 2908)
- Goetz, L. (Box 2909)
- Gog and Magog (Box 2910)
- Gogol, Nikolai (continued) (P) (Box 2911)
- Goikhbarg, Aleksandr (Box 2912)
- Golbertons (Box 2913)
- Gold Paved the Way (Box 2914)
- Goldberger (Box 2915)
- Golden Fleece (Box 2916)
- Golder (Box 2917)
- Goldman, L. (Box 2918)
- Goldring (Box 2919)
- Goldsmith (Box 2920)
- Goldsmith, Oliver (She Stoops to Conquer) (Box 2921)
- Goldstein, J. (Box 2922)
- Golema, Andrej (Box 2923)
- Gollmann, Friedrich Alexander (Box 2924)
- Goltz (Box 2925)
- Gomes (Box 2926)
- Gomez, Thomas (Box 2927)
- Gomez Restrepo (Box 2928)
- Goncalves Viana (Box 2929)
- Gonella, Guido (Box 2930)
- Gonzalez (Box 2931)
- Gonzalez, Nicolas (Box 2932)
- Gonzalez G., Alonso (Box 2933)
- Gonzalez S., Victor A. (Box 2934)
- Good-Bye (Box 2935)
- Goodcell, Henry (Box 2936)
- Goodhue family (Box 2937)
- Goodman, R. (Box 2938)
- Goodrich, Samuel G. (Box 2939)
- Goodwin, H (Box 2940)
- Goodykoontz, Colin B. (Box 2941)
- Gorani, Giuseppe (Box 2942)
- Gordon, Albert I. (Box 2943)
- Gordon, H (Box 2944)
- Gordon, Ronald G. (Box 2945)
- Gore, Michael E. (Box 2946)
- Gori, Pedro (Box 2947)
- Gorky, Maksim (Box 2948)
- Gorn (Box 2949)
- Gorshkov, Georgil S. (Box 2950)
- Goshi Undo Kenkyu (Box 2951)
- Gosse, Edmund W. (Box 2952)
- Gosudarstvennaia (Box 2953)
- Gosudarstvennyi (Box 2954)
- Gosudarstvinnaia (Box 2955)
- Goto (Box 2956)
- Gottfried von Strassburg (Box 2957)
- Gottschalk, Albert (Box 2958)
- Goudsblom, Johan (Box 2959)
- Gould, B. (Box 2960)
- Gould, Terry (Box 2961)
- Gourmont (Box 2962)
- Governess Benevolent Institution (Box 2963)
- Government/press (Box 2964)
- Gow, James (Box 2965)
- Goya, Francisco (Box 2966)
- Graaf, Reinier de (Box 2967)
- Grabill, Wilson H. (Box 2968)
- Grachev, Sergei I. (Box 2969)
- Graduate Institute, Geneva (Box 2970)
- Graesse (Box 2971)
- Graffenried family (Box 2972)
- Graham, Frank (Box 2973)
- Graham, S. (Box 2974)
- Grains (Box 2975)
- Grammar of (Box 2976)
- Gramsci, G. (Box 2977)
- Grand Army of the Republic (author) (Box 2978)
- Grand recueil (Box 2979)
- Grandes idees politiques (Box 2980)
- Grands p. (Box 2981)
- Granite (titles, phrases, etc.) (Box 2982)
- Grant, F. (Box 2983)
- Grant, Robert L. (Box 2984)
- Granville, Mass. (Box 2985)
- Grases (Box 2986)
- Grassl (Box 2987)
- Grav (titles, phrases, etc.) (Box 2988)
- Graves, D. (Box 2989)
- Gravlund (Box 2990)
- Gray, George John (Box 2991)
- Gray, R. (Box 2992)
- Graya (Box 2993)
- Great American (Box 2994)
- Great Britain (Laws, etc.) (L) (Box 2995)
- Great Britain (Laws, etc.), 1649-1660 (Box 2996)
- Great Britain (Treaties, etc.), 1694-1702 (Box 2997)
- Great Britain (Treaties, etc.), 1936 (Edward VIII) (Exchanges of letters) (Box 2998)
- Great Britain. Army. L (Box 2999)
- Great Britain. Army. Royal Tank Corps (Box 3000)
- Great Britain. Board of Agriculture county reports (Fife) (Box 3001)
- Great Britain. British Waterways Board (Box 3002)
- Great Britain. Colonial office (Box 3003)
- Great Britain. Commercial Relations and Exports Department (Box 3004)
- Great Britain. Constitution (Box 3005)
- Great Britain. Court of King's Bench in the Law School (Reports, 1602-1613) (Box 3006)
- Great Britain. Customs Establishment (Box 3007)
- Great Britain. Education department (Box 3008)
- Great Britain. Foreign Office. (continued) (G) (Box 3009)
- Great Britain. General Register Office (Scotland) (Box 3010)
- Great Britain. Irish Parliament (Box 3011)
- Great Britain. Ministry of Food (Box 3012)
- Great Britain. National Gallery (continued) (Box 3013)
- Great Britain. Parliament (author) D (Box 3014)
- Great Britain. Parliament (by date) 1783 (Box 3015)
- Great Britain. Parliament. Commons (author) (Box 3016)
- Great Britain. Parliament. Commons. Secret comm. (Box 3017)
- Great Britain. Parliament. Lords, 1766 (Box 3018)
- Great Britain. Public Record Office (Box 3019)
- Great Britain. Reports. (M) (Box 3020)
- Great Britain. Sea life -- Navy (Box 3021)
- Great Britain. Sovereigns, etc. (K) (continued) (Box 3022)
- Great Britain. Stationery Office (Box 3023)
- Great Britain. Titles, etc. (Box 3024)
- Great inventions (Box 3025)
- Great S. (Box 3026)
- Greatest (Box 3027)
- Greco, L. (Box 3028)
- Greek B. (Box 3029)
- Green, Adwin Wigfall (Box 3030)
- Green, Henry, 1905- (continued) (Box 3031)
- Green, Mason Arnold (Box 3032)
- Green, V. (Box 3033)
- Greenberg (Box 3034)
- Greene, Eleanore D. (Box 3035)
- Greene, Nathaniel (Box 3036)
- Greenheart metropolis (Box 3037)
- Greentree (Box 3038)
- Greer (Box 3039)
- Gregg, T. (Box 3040)
- Gregorovius (Box 3041)
- Gregory, 1852-1932 (continued) (Box 3042)
- Gregory, S.P. (Box 3043)
- Greinz (Box 3044)
- Grenier (Box 3045)
- Gresset (Box 3046)
- Grew (Box 3047)
- Grez (Box 3048)
- Grieco, A. (Box 3049)
- Griffin (Box 3050)
- Griffith, D.D. (Box 3051)
- Griffiths, John R. (Box 3052)
- Grigorii (Box 3053)
- Grim glory (Box 3054)
- Grimm, Heribert (Box 3055)
- Grimoald (Box 3056)
- Grinnell, J. (Box 3057)
- Grismer, M. (Box 3058)
- Griziotti, B. (Box 3059)
- Groenblad (Box 3060)
- Grolier Club (catalogue) (Box 3061)
- Grone (Box 3062)
- Gropallo (Box 3063)
- Gross (surname) (Box 3064)
- Gross (titles, etc.) (Box 3065)
- Grosseteste (Box 3066)
- Grossmith (Box 3067)
- Grot (Box 3068)
- Groton, Mass. (author) (Box 3069)
- Group r. (Box 3070)
- Grove, G. (Box 3071)
- Growth (titles, phrases, etc.) (Box 3072)
- Grubbs (Box 3073)
- Gruen (Box 3074)
- Gruening (Box 3075)
- Grunderwerb (Box 3076)
- Grundrisse (Box 3077)
- Grupe, E. (Box 3078)
- Gruzewski, A. (Box 3079)
- Guacci, C. (Box 3080)
- Guardi, A., 15th Century (Box 3081)
- Guarnotta, A. (Box 3082)
- Guay, Charles (Box 3083)
- Gudiol, Jose (Box 3084)
- Guendel (Box 3085)
- Guenther, Reinhold (Box 3086)
- Guerin de Fremicourt (Box 3087)
- Guerra E. (Box 3088)
- Guerrero, M. (Box 3089)
- Guest, M. (Box 3090)
- Guevara, F. (Box 3091)
- Guhl (Box 3092)
- Guicchardini (Box 3093)
- Guide des… (Box 3094)
- Guide to E. (Box 3095)
- Guide to S. (Box 3096)
- Guide to the S. (Box 3097)
- Guidi (Box 3098)
- Guild (surname) (Box 3099)
- Guillaume (forename) (Box 3100)
- Guillen (Box 3101)
- Guim, Juan Bautista (Box 3102)
- Guinot (Box 3103)
- Guitton (Box 3104)
- Guleke (Box 3105)
- Gulliver (Box 3106)
- Gumppenberg (Box 3107)
- Gunn (Box 3108)
- Gunter (Box 3109)
- Gupta, P. (Box 3110)
- Gurioli (Box 3111)
- Gurudeva (Box 3112)
- Gustaf II Adolf, King of Sweden (Box 3113)
- Gut (Box 3114)
- Guthlac, Saint (Box 3115)
- Gutierrez, Leandro (Box 3116)
- Gutmann, O. (Box 3117)
- Gutzmann (Box 3118)
- Guyot (Box 3119)
- Guzman G., Hugo (Box 3120)
- Gwynn, S. (Box 3121)
- Gyosai (Box 3122)
- H., M. (Box 3123)
- H.P. (Box 3124)
- Haags Gemeentemuseum (Box 3125)
- Haas (Box 3126)
- Haass (Box 3127)
- Haberman (Box 3128)
- Habits (Box 3129)
- Hacia las (Box 3130)
- Hacklaender (Box 3131)
- Hadding, A. (Box 3132)
- Hadith-Dictionaries (Box 3133)
- Hadron interactions (Box 3134)
- Haegg, E. (Box 3135)
- Haer, F. (Box 3136)
- Hafenbar (Box 3137)
- Hagadah shel Pesah (Box 3138)
- Hagen, F. (Box 3139)
- Haggai, S. (Box 3140)
- Hagner (Box 3141)
- Hague. Perm. Court of International Justice. Bibliography (Box 3142)
- Hahn, R. (Box 3143)
- Hai ou (Box 3144)
- Haig, M. (Box 3145)
- Haiman (Box 3146)
- Haiti (author) (Box 3147)
- Hak Sri… (Box 3148)
- Hakobu (Box 3149)
- Halbe (Box 3150)
- Hale (surname) (Box 3151)
- Hale, P. (Box 3152)
- Halvey, Ludovic (Box 3153)
- Halifax, G. (Box 3154)
- Hall, C.B. (Box 3155)
- Hall, Francis (Box 3156)
- Hall, John, 1829-1898 (Box 3157)
- Hall, Peter F. (Box 3158)
- Hall, Winfield Scott (Box 3159)
- Hallel (Box 3160)
- Hallett, H.F. (Box 3161)
- Hallman (Box 3162)
- Halper, B. (Box 3163)
- Halsey, S.H. (Box 3164)
- Hamadah, Ibrahim (Box 3165)
- Hambly (Box 3166)
- Hamburger (titles, etc.) (Box 3167)
- Hamden H. (Box 3168)
- Hamid Tahir (Box 3169)
- Hamilton, Cosmo (Box 3170)
- Hamilton, Joseph (Box 3171)
- Hamilton family (Box 3172)
- Hammacher (Box 3173)
- Hammer ring. Phonodisc (Box 3174)
- Hammond, Charles (Box 3175)
- Hammond panoramic… (Box 3176)
- Hampson, E.L. (Box 3177)
- Han (Box 3178)
- Han, Kuo-huang (Box 3179)
- Han, Wei (Box 3180)
- Hanafi, Mahmud (Box 3181)
- Hancock, W. (Box 3182)
- Handbook of American Literature (Box 3183)
- Handbook of new (Box 3184)
- Handbooks (Box 3185)
- Handbuch der physik (Box 3186)
- Handel, G. (Box 3187)
- Handlirsch, G. (Box 3188)
- Haney (Box 3189)
- Hanguk komunhwa nongo (Box 3190)
- Hanji no techo (Box 3191)
- Hanna (Box 3192)
- Hannibal, H. (Box 3193)
- Hans (Box 3194)
- Hansen, E. (Box 3195)
- Hansford (Box 3196)
- Hanss, M. (Box 3197)
- Hao ko ch'iu (Box 3198)
- Haque, R. (Box 3199)
- Harang, L. (Box 3200)
- Harbison, F. (Box 3201)
- Hardar saga (Box 3202)
- Harding, C. (Box 3203)
- Hardt (Box 3204)
- Hardy, M. (Box 3205)
- Hardy, W. (Box 3206)
- Haret, S. (Box 3207)
- Harimau (Box 3208)
- Harkness, J. (Box 3209)
- Harlez (Box 3210)
- Harmon, R.S. (Box 3211)
- Harnack, Adolf von (subject) (Box 3212)
- Harper (surname) (Box 3213)
- Harper's (Box 3214)
- Harriman, M. (Box 3215)
- Harris, Charles William (Box 3216)
- Harris, James Rendel (continued) (Box 3217)
- Harris, Matthias (Box 3218)
- Harris, W.A. (Box 3219)
- Harrison, E. (Box 3220)
- Harrison, Lloyd (Box 3221)
- Harrisse, Henry. (E) (Box 3222)
- Harsh, C. (Box 3223)
- Hart, Horace (Box 3224)
- Hart, Samuel (Box 3225)
- Harte, R. (Box 3226)
- Hartford theological (Box 3227)
- Hartley, Mary (Box 3228)
- Hartmann, Eduard, 1842-1906 (subject) (Box 3229)
- Hartmann, W. (Box 3230)
- Hartung, H. (Box 3231)
- Harvard bibliographies (Box 3232)
- Harvard hist. studies (Box 3233)
- Harvard studies in English (Box 3234)
- Harvard University. Bussey Institute (Box 3235)
- Harvard University. Graduate school of business (Box 3236)
- Harvard University. Observatory (Box 3237)
- Harvard-Yenching Institute. Studies (Box 3238)
- Harvey, Jane (Box 3239)
- Harwood (surname) (Box 3240)
- Hasan Rumlu (Box 3241)
- Haselberg (Box 3242)
- Hashknife (Box 3243)
- Hasler (Box 3244)
- Hasse, E. (Box 3245)
- Hasting (surname) (Box 3246)
- Hatai, S. (Box 3247)
- Hatfield, J. (Box 3248)
- Hatterfly, J. (Box 3249)
- Hauck (Box 3250)
- Hauk (Box 3251)